{
    "user_name": "Susanna",
    "session_complete_time": "2018-12-04 19:16:35.283042",
    "session_pk": 12,
    "session_size": 6,
    "block_size": 6,
    "policy_id": 3,
    "block_data": [
        {
            "block_id": 52,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 309,
                    "question_pk": 1259,
                    "question": "The fact that others now have the freedom to make that choice is something I'm very proud of.",
                    "chunk": "make that choice ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Treffen Sie diese Wahl",
                    "answer": "make that choice",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 310,
                    "question_pk": 251,
                    "question": "I now volunteer in schools and hospitals, dancing and talking about my leg; I do motivational speaking and teach dance classes as well as playing in my band.",
                    "chunk": "teach dance classes ",
                    "chunk_translation": "unterrichten Sie Tanzkurse",
                    "answer": "teaching dance classes",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 311,
                    "question_pk": 722,
                    "question": "The boys were really uncertain  they felt nature should take its course  and Becky went very quiet.",
                    "chunk": "should take its course  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "sollte seinen Lauf nehmen",
                    "answer": "should take its course",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 312,
                    "question_pk": 56,
                    "question": "My daughter and grandson got the same one at the same time  and the tattoo artist even did the same one on his own leg.",
                    "chunk": "did the same one on his own leg",
                    "chunk_translation": "machte dasselbe auf seinem eigenen Bein",
                    "answer": "did the same one on his own leg",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 313,
                    "question_pk": 606,
                    "question": "When I had to write anything down, I guessed, forming what I hoped were the right words.",
                    "chunk": "forming what I hoped were the right words",
                    "chunk_translation": "was ich hoffte, waren die richtigen Worte",
                    "answer": "what I hoped were the right word forms",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 314,
                    "question_pk": 114,
                    "question": "But the real achievement is not what I've done; it's how long I've lived.",
                    "chunk": "is not what I've done",
                    "chunk_translation": "ist nicht was ich getan habe",
                    "answer": "is not what I've done",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 53,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 315,
                    "question_pk": 288,
                    "question": "When we were skiing and snowboarding down, I wanted to be at the front to get fresh tracks.",
                    "chunk": "be at the front to get fresh tracks",
                    "chunk_translation": "an der Front sein, um neue Spuren zu bekommen",
                    "answer": "be at the front to get fresh tracks",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 316,
                    "question_pk": 336,
                    "question": "When I didn't answer, they started to look for me.",
                    "chunk": "to look for me",
                    "chunk_translation": "nach mir zu suchen",
                    "answer": "to look for me",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 317,
                    "question_pk": 156,
                    "question": "It was during a production in 2009 at university, where I was studying musical theatre, that I started to feel pain in my right leg.",
                    "chunk": "in my right leg",
                    "chunk_translation": "in meinem rechten Bein",
                    "answer": "in my right leg",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 318,
                    "question_pk": 743,
                    "question": "I knelt down and put one hand around the back of the lamb's head and one on its chest, so my hands were slightly inside.",
                    "chunk": "one on its chest",
                    "chunk_translation": "eine auf seiner Brust",
                    "answer": "one on its chest",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 319,
                    "question_pk": 130,
                    "question": "I tried abseiling recently, as part of a family fun day.",
                    "chunk": "of a family fun day",
                    "chunk_translation": "eines Familienspa\u00dftages",
                    "answer": "of a fun family day",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 320,
                    "question_pk": 457,
                    "question": "There was traffic on the road and, although I was pretty out of it, I knew we weren't going to make it to the hospital.",
                    "chunk": "going to make it to the hospital",
                    "chunk_translation": "werde es ins Krankenhaus schaffen",
                    "answer": "going to make it to the hospital",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 54,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 321,
                    "question_pk": 658,
                    "question": "It was back to basics on the course.",
                    "chunk": "basics on the course",
                    "chunk_translation": "Grundlagen auf dem Kurs",
                    "answer": "basics on the course",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 322,
                    "question_pk": 474,
                    "question": "Richard returned seconds later with three doctors and a wheelchair, but by the time they arrived the baby was already crowning and I couldn't be moved.",
                    "chunk": "I couldn't be moved",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich konnte nicht bewegt werden",
                    "answer": "I couldn't be moved",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 323,
                    "question_pk": 843,
                    "question": "I was still hoping this was nothing, but when I saw a woman crying on the street, I knew the situation was serious.",
                    "chunk": "was still hoping this was nothing",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich hoffte immer noch, dass das nichts war",
                    "answer": "was still hoping this was nothing",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 324,
                    "question_pk": 667,
                    "question": "I had a laptop with read-and-write and speak-and-spell programs.",
                    "chunk": "read-and-write and speak-and-spell programs",
                    "chunk_translation": "Lese- und Schreib- und Sprach- und Buchstabierprogramme",
                    "answer": "read-and-write and speak-and-spell programmes",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 325,
                    "question_pk": 879,
                    "question": "All the experts we were calling told us the safe was airtight and he was going to die.",
                    "chunk": "we were calling ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Wir haben angerufen",
                    "answer": "we were calling",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 326,
                    "question_pk": 1166,
                    "question": "With help from my then boyfriend and now husband, Scott, who is a computer networking engineer, I was able to send CGM data to my phone via a laptop.",
                    "chunk": "is a computer networking engineer",
                    "chunk_translation": "ist ein Computer-Networking-Ingenieur",
                    "answer": "is a computer networking engineer",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 55,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 327,
                    "question_pk": 619,
                    "question": "It was brilliant  practical and physical.",
                    "chunk": "was brilliant  practical and physical",
                    "chunk_translation": "war brilliant praktisch und k\u00f6rperlich",
                    "answer": "was brilliant practical and physical",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 328,
                    "question_pk": 310,
                    "question": "Everything was white, and I thought, Is this one of these dreams where I almost die?",
                    "chunk": "Everything was white, and I thought",
                    "chunk_translation": "Alles war wei\u00df und ich dachte",
                    "answer": "Everything was white and I thought",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 329,
                    "question_pk": 1025,
                    "question": "The handlebars of the zip line had caught in the V of a tree branch.",
                    "chunk": "the V of a tree branch",
                    "chunk_translation": "das V eines Baumastes",
                    "answer": "the V of a tree branch",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 330,
                    "question_pk": 524,
                    "question": "Everybody was so kind  the driver, the doctors, the paramedics  I can't thank them enough.",
                    "chunk": "I can't thank them enough",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich kann ihnen nicht genug danken",
                    "answer": "I can't thank them enough",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 331,
                    "question_pk": 276,
                    "question": "In 2012, I was 22 and doing a ski season in Ischgl, Austria.",
                    "chunk": "a ski season ",
                    "chunk_translation": "eine Skisaison",
                    "answer": "a skiing season",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 332,
                    "question_pk": 656,
                    "question": "They set me up with an educational psychologist, who told me that my peer group outranked me by 15 years.",
                    "chunk": "my peer group ",
                    "chunk_translation": "meine Peer-Gruppe",
                    "answer": "my peer group",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 56,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 333,
                    "question_pk": 992,
                    "question": "My husband and I were excited as the cruise ship pulled into its final stop, a small port in Mexico, in April 2016.",
                    "chunk": "a small port ",
                    "chunk_translation": "ein kleiner Hafen",
                    "answer": "a small port",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 334,
                    "question_pk": 655,
                    "question": "I applied to do a degree, biological medicine and health sciences, at the Open University.",
                    "chunk": "a degree, biological medicine and health sciences, ",
                    "chunk_translation": "ein Abschluss, biologische Medizin und Gesundheitswissenschaften,",
                    "answer": "a biological medicine and health science degree",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 335,
                    "question_pk": 1088,
                    "question": "I knew the ship would be leaving at 5pm and didn't want to be left behind, especially as our passports were onboard.",
                    "chunk": "the ship would be leaving at 5pm ",
                    "chunk_translation": "das Schiff w\u00fcrde um 17 Uhr verlassen",
                    "answer": "the ship would be leaving at 5 pm",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 336,
                    "question_pk": 650,
                    "question": "He urged me to get back into education.",
                    "chunk": "get back into education",
                    "chunk_translation": "zur\u00fcck in Bildung",
                    "answer": "get back into education",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 337,
                    "question_pk": 902,
                    "question": "Next, we had to work out the combination: blindly opening the safe by force might have hurt or suffocated the boy.",
                    "chunk": "opening the safe by force ",
                    "chunk_translation": "\u00d6ffnen Sie den Safe mit Gewalt",
                    "answer": "opening the safe by force",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 338,
                    "question_pk": 75,
                    "question": "After that, I started to think about what else I could do to raise money and awareness for different charities.",
                    "chunk": "money and awareness ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Geld und Bewusstsein",
                    "answer": "money and awareness",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 57,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 339,
                    "question_pk": 668,
                    "question": "I had a laptop with read-and-write and speak-and-spell programs.",
                    "chunk": "with read-and-write and speak-and-spell programs",
                    "chunk_translation": "mit Lese- und Schreibprogrammen und Speak-and-Spell-Programmen",
                    "answer": "with speak-and-spell and read-and-write programs",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 340,
                    "question_pk": 1127,
                    "question": "I used to love lying in on weekends.",
                    "chunk": "to love lying in on weekends",
                    "chunk_translation": "Lieber am Wochenende liegen",
                    "answer": "to love lying in on weekends",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 341,
                    "question_pk": 720,
                    "question": "The boys were really uncertain  they felt nature should take its course  and Becky went very quiet.",
                    "chunk": "its course  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "sein Verlauf",
                    "answer": "its course",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 342,
                    "question_pk": 324,
                    "question": "It was horrible, lying there not being able to move, nobody knowing where I was or having any way of finding me.",
                    "chunk": "having any way of finding me",
                    "chunk_translation": "Irgendeine M\u00f6glichkeit, mich zu finden",
                    "answer": "having any way of finding me",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 343,
                    "question_pk": 1147,
                    "question": "Once I went to college and lived alone, this became a bigger problem; I was increasingly afraid of going to sleep at night.",
                    "chunk": "going to sleep at night",
                    "chunk_translation": "nachts schlafen gehen",
                    "answer": "going to sleep at night",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 344,
                    "question_pk": 136,
                    "question": "I've got a few ideas for the next charity challenge on my 106th birthday on 6 April, but nothing has been confirmed yet.",
                    "chunk": "my 106th birthday ",
                    "chunk_translation": "mein 106. Geburtstag",
                    "answer": "my 106th birthday",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}